<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<user>
    <description>Tweets by FT companies editor @brookeamasters and her team. Our customer service team is @FTcare.</description>
    <following>214604553</following>
    <following>14519041</following>
    <following>17093617</following>
    <following>61808337</following>
    <following>16513997</following>
    <following>15135214</following>
    <following>1295561</following>
    <following>11023052</following>
    <following>53373487</following>
    <following>59736898</following>
    <following>51088856</following>
    <following>15866793</following>
    <following>18949512</following>
    <following>20237824</following>
    <following>15861355</following>
    <following>15861220</following>
    <following>18949452</following>
    <following>46417793</following>
    <following>31714599</following>
    <following>46357879</following>
    <following>17133897</following>
    <following>45542386</following>
    <following>40259056</following>
    <following>4898091</following>
    <following>14074886</following>
    <following>14074967</following>
    <following>10977192</following>
    <following>11013952</following>
    <friends>17093617</friends>
    <friends>61808337</friends>
    <friends>11023052</friends>
    <friends>59736898</friends>
    <friends>51088856</friends>
    <friends>18949512</friends>
    <friends>15861355</friends>
    <friends>18949452</friends>
    <friends>46417793</friends>
    <friends>31714599</friends>
    <friends>46357879</friends>
    <friends>40259056</friends>
    <friends>4898091</friends>
    <friends>14074886</friends>
    <friends>14074967</friends>
    <friends>10977192</friends>
    <friends>11013952</friends>
    <id>ftfinancenews</id>
    <location></location>
    <name>Finance News</name>
    <tweets>
Countrywide shares rise on positive revenues https://t.co/hTGcjrL7KW
Worldpay founder to launch challenger bank https://t.co/dVan30knJJ
Never mind the quality, feel the width https://t.co/9EGbqnmnCR
FSB sets out blueprint to make asset management safer https://t.co/AXUuBAf1Op
Five things to look out for in the US bank earnings https://t.co/pzeNCVjv8o
Bharti Airtel opens banks in mobile phone shops https://t.co/S15EFMY5Ax
UBI Banca offers €1 for 3 rescued Italian lenders https://t.co/BItzpXLtlP
Lloyds customers hit by second day of IT glitch https://t.co/h6wV7LjKcB
UniCredit: paying up https://t.co/szHnmAdQAK
EU equivalence is the City’s next Brexit battle https://t.co/rVDcjffbVP
Morgan Stanley execs netted $17m in share sales https://t.co/w9UUlWmtc9
How Trump’s wall could affect property prices https://t.co/pH8n86LNvG
Barratt builds fewer homes in London https://t.co/5PUDiSxYxN
Lombard:  Sainsbury’s Argos plan avoids catalogue of errors https://t.co/PNeoiVnIeh
Binary trader winds down after regulatory issues https://t.co/LhZgpACIen
CAA sells pension liabilities to PIC https://t.co/PQDfUl4U8y
Funding Circle raises £82m from global investors https://t.co/V3andSyVIi
City lobbying group drops demand for EU ‘passport’’ https://t.co/G0Jed6UdB8
US lawmakers challenge Wells over overdraft charges https://t.co/Az2b10sDsw
What Wall Street wants from Trump https://t.co/OOa2uPl3Ee
Activist hedge funds profit amid market volatility https://t.co/AxLEUphEpq
City chiefs call for 3-year delay to Brexit https://t.co/WUD3xkA9cH
Silicon Valley start-ups fall behind in VC funding https://t.co/jOa88m3fRQ
China groups insured against blocked foreign deals https://t.co/chk4BMyMr4
Tech funding: snap decision https://t.co/scPcuTYepT
Size matters in Russia banks as profitability returns https://t.co/22OlHPIAfQ
Taylor Wimpey bullish on 2016 profits https://t.co/LNICPGkyeC
Foxtons expects drop in profits on London slowdown https://t.co/PR0vJL9Qkx
Lombard:  Supermarkets offer a foretaste of full-year sales https://t.co/mbqPGxHri0
Value of reported fraud in UK financial services falls sharply https://t.co/Bg7Mhwmzdh
Sale of Bradford &amp; Bingley mortgages nears end https://t.co/kSwqBK0eOm
Size matters in Russian banking as profitability returns https://t.co/3BwbA19j89
FRC seeks more power with boards https://t.co/3lAD9F71OW
Draghi and Renzi targets of alleged hacking operation https://t.co/6UyLk7n0Pn
Bovis Homes buyers hit out at quality of new houses https://t.co/g0aHUijOyQ
US oil and gas industry spending set to surge https://t.co/AfWWEtCzzt
Ringfencing will help in the next banking crisis https://t.co/fenQXKbsEa
Spencer sells bulk of TP ICAP stake for £200m https://t.co/uJE4BSszjG
London mayor intervenes in rejected 490-home projects https://t.co/VkKfHmwlfO
DoJ to charge UK-based traders in forex-rig probe https://t.co/jVzE20O9si
Banking Weekly podcast: Bank reform postponed, UK ringfence concerns and US banks’ credit outlook https://t.co/8WHPrDp9Go
Italy’s shrinking bad debts give rise to optimism https://t.co/imJhsUx1pB
Fosun to lift its stake in Millennium BCP to 30% https://t.co/KSq7vYezJB
Prime property predictions for 2017: Nathan Brooker https://t.co/f5MdNm8A5t
Blockchain receives its first big test case https://t.co/89IEaDWlwn
Lombard:  William Hill finds guidance a game of two halves https://t.co/ZRvnDkf7Vb
Three alternative sources of investment yield https://t.co/v75jHCOHAi
Deutsche Bank turns to social media to hire talent https://t.co/UA9JUEyRvJ
Trump names son-in-law as his senior adviser https://t.co/PjbOvYNY6y
IG Group sanguine over French regulations https://t.co/KYhXdZXqjR
BofA sued by US regulator over ‘unpaid premiums’ https://t.co/Vdw9bxAe2s
Bovis: cold steel https://t.co/lLc0jR1TjL
Government no longer largest shareholder in Lloyds https://t.co/o23xHjjX0v
Bank risk weights: cheesed off https://t.co/QXDJHNyils
Orix chief seeks Trump boom https://t.co/BoOxJRlyFy
Prime property predictions for 2017: Savills https://t.co/L8Fr2Rn1G7
Wells Fargo counts cost of sham accounts scandal https://t.co/HwvqOVboka
Deutsche and UniCredit look to tap investors https://t.co/eQVWuJCIVD
Asian private banks target next generation of super-rich https://t.co/ZPQHr3Eu6H
Asian private banks target next generation of super-rich https://t.co/GK2I6jXzZn
Asian private banks target next generation of super-rich https://t.co/lSrJrEHiey
Bovis Homes chief departs after profit warning https://t.co/qlxOh5cHq8
China P2P lenders brace for regulatory crackdown https://t.co/CxRcfiJpYZ
Mezzanine funds poised to take up the slack https://t.co/BtpqriEp7m
Bernard Matthews pension shortfall probed https://t.co/SkQkQfiiYD
Biggest banks in line for $200m regulatory costs https://t.co/o9wf4RLM3N
Fed official says jobs data rule out fiscal boost https://t.co/Iuxi4m8S73
Fed official says jobs data rule out fiscal boost https://t.co/u8SQefPgxC
Morningstar ups competition with asset managers https://t.co/sSeWN9Y2Bk
Morgan Stanley in talks to sell oil tanker stake https://t.co/wicQbHMYe0
Smaller companies fear threat from new financial regulation https://t.co/0N83S5ocRX
Hedge fund launches heading for eight-year low https://t.co/LQOFKAkLoS
US tax reform is vital but Trump’s plan is flawed https://t.co/chw0GdS5tT
Berkeley eyes Birmingham as London house prices fall https://t.co/Xakihz36Cj
Mnuchin faces tough road en route to US Treasury https://t.co/MsxaRegN8G
Payments chief ousted as PE seeks rapid growth https://t.co/i6Kp62Emlj
Banks rush to bond market ahead of rates rise https://t.co/i7EO20JNQG
BoE told to firm up oversight of clearing https://t.co/8nvx6GNRW3
Week Ahead: January 8-14 https://t.co/xzUOnLT5Kk
UK regulators concerned over bank ‘ringfence’ compliance https://t.co/pXtihvIZgF
Insurers tap cyber security ratings https://t.co/mh6lJMTqap
UK investors pull £31bn from equities and bonds https://t.co/cvw3EK3a7S
Industry frustrated by EU retail regulation saga https://t.co/I4s61aHL5w
The best- and worst-selling funds of 2016 https://t.co/ccVshY0RZ2
Trump son-in-law held talks with Chinese tycoon https://t.co/fIj5md5vCG
Five reasons why investors are buckling up for 2017 https://t.co/ArGM4SlmxO
Economists hit back at claims of crisis after post-Brexit misses https://t.co/Fk367KyQko
Tricky tax equity erodes US infrastructure boom https://t.co/P9x4hMa9Ba
Bumpy road for Chinese driverless car ambitions https://t.co/mP8aD9R9hm
What’s the best zero rate credit card deal? https://t.co/ElkmTFpcUl
Carlyle to sell health business Nature’s Bounty https://t.co/TuwtXeSpwB
Rise in trading activity after Trump victory spurs TP ICAP https://t.co/woEzYLPzaR
Lombard:  Persimmon sees quicker plan for building on margin https://t.co/kDHsnH3wD8
Lombard:  Wolfson’s escalating problems at Next https://t.co/VyQXGsQIEM
Housebuilding will be a test of May’s resolve https://t.co/nqCkfoaccK
Payday lender Dollar for sale as rules tighten https://t.co/QZax5RLUIX
Brief respite from peso pain after intervention https://t.co/bjkULK4mN4
Robey Warshaw: three men on a roll https://t.co/E7m4NYpKgJ
Novo Banco: damaged goods https://t.co/LZx95Tiety
Head of Barclays Japan questioned in Libor probe https://t.co/9T6nU2pplj
New Swedish business king takes the long-term view https://t.co/fW2CFxO46P
It was a great year for investors, not hedge funds https://t.co/gxweZtwiQg
Prime property predictions for 2017 https://t.co/LroJo835rZ
Bank of Cyprus free to resume dividend https://t.co/qdHdEMDFtq
Lone Star enters final talks to acquire Novo Banco https://t.co/bJVtm87Whk
Persimmon reports strong demand post Brexit vote https://t.co/JvEwVSybhY
High land prices drive China property M&amp;A spurt https://t.co/6x26uMGGuJ
Ireland’s central bank flexes regulatory muscles https://t.co/TsQtqGXap5
Global cartel fines hit new high, powered by $4.1bn in EU https://t.co/vxVZTBZ5v8
Funding Circle secures financing from UK government https://t.co/2Mz6FZdIhP
ING-DiBa thrives online amid German banking difficulties https://t.co/8svlpszKVE
German push for home ownership drives bubble fears https://t.co/tAEnbhUN53
Trump names Wall Street lawyer to head SEC https://t.co/KI0WV0FgYB
Hillhouse invests $250m in US software provider https://t.co/qdZZCdxO2M
Deutsche Bank’s financial crime head steps down https://t.co/xpVC0ErcJq
LSE sells French clearing unit to Euronext for €510m https://t.co/qOKX8j0gCI
MasterCard deal to buy Vocalink raises competition concerns https://t.co/Xps0tyzEX7
China/US real estate: safe as houses https://t.co/nhvkXvaE5k
Early-mover online estate agents pushed out https://t.co/jglOqhAzOd
Automated advisers: short circuit https://t.co/q4XFm6Frf5
UK brokers feel squeeze as Aim’s ranks decline https://t.co/8ZFzisuQUk
China clamps down on ‘exotic’ insurance https://t.co/Gqn1POMe65
Cantor Fitzgerald: Jain’s addiction https://t.co/YCHWrQb2PB
Brexit set to weigh on property prices in 2017 https://t.co/ajGbvyATEz
UK companies look to sell off pension liabilities https://t.co/tvEZiVly3f
How much should we save to retire at 60? https://t.co/DeQi2HTazX
Equifax and TransUnion fined for deceptive practices https://t.co/O4mQANIAjp
Berkshire takes on Hartford’s $1.5bn asbestos risk https://t.co/TqmYG651ld
Indonesia: pride of place https://t.co/SnyeXQ8h04
Megamergers off menu as insurers eye next targets https://t.co/rOt8zuoqC2
Banco Popular faces test to rid itself of toxic legacy https://t.co/og7fVSx6ao
Chinese insurers feel pressure to rein in deals https://t.co/4y3FjaTjwH
JPMorgan in row with Indonesia over debt rating https://t.co/fIbFiDBeJr
Bourses kick off 2017 on front foot https://t.co/cuAx3Pg893
US bank faces profits hit from interest rate rise https://t.co/Jrdbjf7Dsu
Basel postpones bank reform vote https://t.co/2uQy87NLDT
FTSE 100’s record run gathers pace https://t.co/7yPuNTEd0c
Russia: Inside the private bank backed by the state https://t.co/yajyBf00Dx
ANZ sells stake in Shanghai bank for A$1.8bn https://t.co/tHI5XOyxfZ
Foreign fund managers struggle for China foothold https://t.co/5JywOAvxj6
New Bank Pekao owner vows to keep it independent https://t.co/oAMJ8GpmzY
Anshu Jain joins Cantor Fitzgerald as president https://t.co/FlDSyInlgH
Reinsurers braced for year of cost-cutting https://t.co/cayTlCwc7q
Banks’ overdraft fees have critics seeing red https://t.co/nZIH8thceO
Cancellations have hurt the economy https://t.co/MNfOT1yzFp
Wells Fargo’s overdraft income surges ahead of rivals https://t.co/LJUIlzjKdk
‘Garden villages’ to create thousands of UK homes https://t.co/4DUDlsWZdR
China tightens control of personal forex purchases https://t.co/fBV3pNqhLV
Cashless society inflates bank statements https://t.co/hue06IL1LC
Newly created TP ICAP looks to lead voice broking https://t.co/7lrPtYusRo
UK banks in credit card and loan ‘frenzy’ https://t.co/mhC92sttmR
Corporate moments to look out for in 2017 https://t.co/71AwNWLgr5
Singapore fund buys into UK commercial property https://t.co/dZg75ArKCY
RBS urged to create shareholder committee https://t.co/N7XQALaYsy
Beijing mayor promises end to house prices rise https://t.co/7b1CQq3nEf
M&amp;A boom set to continue in 2017 https://t.co/WvYHZD5QhJ
SEC scrutinises sale of Mozambique ‘tuna bond’ https://t.co/ATg7rQZNNc
Greece: A question of independence https://t.co/PiRWPdy0Mw
US mortgage refinancings head for 17 year low https://t.co/ZZpDZjzIFZ
Chinese M&amp;A boom faces regulatory checks https://t.co/Ojmd6ECzSz
Final quarter of blockbuster deals boosts M&amp;A activity https://t.co/f2whCOOMEB
Switzerland moves further to end bank secrecy https://t.co/tV7vSmozEc
Boom in cyber attack insurance predicted to gather pace https://t.co/YpBKlRKuND
Nationwide warns of UK house price slowdown in 2017 https://t.co/amodboSWAw
Chinese keep buying London property despite Brexit https://t.co/49P8igjC70
US mutual fund launches hit by changing landscape https://t.co/dWvRtjCivx
Law firms rush to boost defences after China hack https://t.co/3Q3HkOjc9w
Williams &amp; Glyn sale faces Bank of England review https://t.co/azoslY6jps
Hong Kong and New York battle for IPO dominance https://t.co/6eluYOxSQa
Indian banks issue cash withdrawal warning https://t.co/RIH3axw4YO
RBS disposal: no fairy tale ending https://t.co/ZdhpeilId0
Ukraine takes needed steps to clean up its banks https://t.co/SkCS4ahGGl
Bovis shares slide on warning of December slowdown https://t.co/gp5kntRRxU
German states battle over tax avoidance clampdown https://t.co/J3EcfhMxMk
Lloyds ready to set up European arm post-Brexit https://t.co/uMv3jenDrn
Housing market set to stall next year, says Halifax https://t.co/wgyKHQQR7K
Chinese hackers charged with US law firms theft https://t.co/ka2KMPjUfD
BoJ’s stimulus breadcrumb trail leads to Reit ETFs https://t.co/i9XEpKPQj3
Macri turns to fiscal hawk in Argentina reshuffle https://t.co/YNNCEJlLt7
Nonbanks shake up the Dutch mortgage market https://t.co/dSMTW73zqJ
RBS considers reducing senior staff bonuses https://t.co/PSNPgUMQhd
Halcyon days over for investment banks https://t.co/Gwo9LrRiBc
Peer-to-peer lenders morph into traditional banking https://t.co/T0MmZQDc3o
German, French stocks near double-digit gains for quarter https://t.co/hTUEnGc2UK
Chinese billionaire with eye on redrawing investment https://t.co/D0IXERkDrS
Monte dei Paschi shortfall hits €8bn, says ECB https://t.co/pPEpGPgkbe
HSBC should show way forward with a female chairman https://t.co/iVFB6n8Xge
Five industries under threat from technology https://t.co/9ITDnGc5Ha
China lease renewals ease homeowner fears https://t.co/NxbQmz6gV5
Corporate year in review https://t.co/UBgG9bDje0
A bailout of Monte dei Paschi is not enough https://t.co/AlEvTHkIfE
Banks add spice to year’s No (and Yes) questions https://t.co/IsdG0giTZN
London’s luxury rentals hit by relocation slowdown https://t.co/mObOgryiqq</tweets>
    <tweetsFollowing>
RT @JohnJHarwood: "According to US govt official, Flynn phoned Russian Ambassador several times the day Obama  announced retaliation" https…
RT @NickSquires1: Horrendous acid attack on former Miss #Italy contestant shines spotlight on violence against women.
https://t.co/D3Cy9zPR…
Sweet, Paul Ryan is happy this man is alive. He just doesn't think he should have a right to healthcare *in the fut… https://t.co/dmAy3FgDow
RT @swajones: #Spain's beloved fictional detective #PepeCarvalho to return in new book years after creator's death https://t.co/370b6yKzx2
RT @annafifield: Japan has seen a sudden increase in syphilis cases. So it's enlisting anime star Sailor Moon to fight it. Of course. https…
RT @nycsouthpaw: And then there's this. https://t.co/qZFtcgaegO https://t.co/5rhzfb1DQA
Justice department to review FBI's conduct in Clinton email inquiry https://t.co/mAoQfF6r6C
France's far-right leader Marine Le Pen seen at Trump Tower https://t.co/40zq79LXNW
RT @DrMiguelPerales: Pls RT &amp; help my 12 yr old daughter's @Change petition "End Gender Stereotypes on @Microsoft Word" https://t.co/BwhuCU…
RT @washingtonpost: 200 buses have applied for city parking on Inauguration Day. 1,200 have applied for the Women’s March.
https://t.co/iWM…</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
@LankyYabba @nthurlbeck I thought it was him - That's Life!
RT @nthurlbeck: Expect to see this quite a lot tomorrow. Christopher Steele, the former MI6 man behind the Trump dossier https://t.co/oikUx…
Idea: a GOP-Obamacare themed cobbler called Re-heel and Re-lace.
@jaketapper Did CNN link to the BuzzFeed doc dump, as @KellyannePolls suggested last night? I can't see it in the online story.
@herman_james @alexnfranks yep it's in Brooklyn at Barclays Center
@herman_james you ready for the DeGale fight on Sat? I've got a ticket!
RT @anatomymedia: Listen to ANATOMY's @g_mirabelli speak with @MattGarrahan about what it takes for media brands to be successful. #Podcast…
RT @juleshyman: MARINE LE PEN IS AT TRUMP TOWER
Special White House discount! Call now for 25 per cent off your next pair of LLBean boots https://t.co/kWWK6TCiaZ
RT @gideonrachman: Touching that ex-spook who did Trump research, asked the neighbour to feed his cats, before going into hiding. Very Jame…</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
You know when you see a Tweet that's just, brilliant? Here are the Tweets we wish we wrote: https://t.co/gUVpZ481Co https://t.co/KW1EKaJ1WS
What should you post on Instagram? https://t.co/xsJMXQ15B8 6 types of content that work https://t.co/V7eSs9pS1E
Make the most of GIFs in your social media strategy: https://t.co/46PhWT7ceE The ultimate GIF guide https://t.co/VhJ9ALTURd
Want to increase your Twitter engagement? Here's a 5-day plan: https://t.co/qHRJQBgiCj https://t.co/F2HG95Bv25
Strapped for time and ideas? There’s no need to panic: https://t.co/b5HdOiElMd 10 content ideas that work https://t.co/beLO4XEGFw
How to launch and grow your YouTube channel subscribers and views in 14 days: https://t.co/rPkPB7icXN https://t.co/nYO3BJHyv4
Have you been neglecting your LinkedIn profile? https://t.co/AgCRG2fOY6 5 easy ways to refresh your LinkedIn https://t.co/x0ZkINbDKU
Before you hit send on that social media post, ask yourself these 5 questions: https://t.co/abVNSF3WDR https://t.co/ZgoKKlpbRu
@GroundsYVR We really did! The whole office got a chance to enjoy them 👍
@evernote It's always a pleasure to spend the #HootChat hour discussing ideas with you!</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
.@DameStephanie_: Blazing a trail for women in tech https://t.co/e1RtNzIp9f
Business Book Challenge – a masterclass https://t.co/AJeiIByG9z
The Life of a Song: Stairway to Heaven https://t.co/d9XIoheXH2
Leaders under pressure: Denis Kozlowski 4/4 https://t.co/oly2gKMYfT
Leaders under pressure: Marcela Sapone https://t.co/B7CYFhT4gs
‘Pig-killing day’ by David Szalay https://t.co/MOBIm0pyiU
Leaders under pressure: Stephen Hester 2/4 https://t.co/HNYySHahWl
Leaders under pressure: Pascal Soriot 1/4 https://t.co/HKKlyWI7Px
2016 politics review https://t.co/ZbrVlDSGEq</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
RT @timoreilly: I’d missed this good piece by @ranaforoohar. This is a message that bears repeating, again and again. https://t.co/aXbZDukm…
yes indeed..... https://t.co/SRqWApY7E3
Pork pie No.1 is built and being eaten. Very good reviews so far. Pie No.2 to be constructed in the morning. https://t.co/HUlJUmcB02
Thanks to your disgusting council we shall in future be spending our money elsewhere.  @RBKingston #surbitoncrescent https://t.co/9DB8RPbg2U
Looking forward to a splendid lunch with retired FT colleagues today. (If ever there was a bunch of folks who could put the world right)
@SadiqKhan has a real nerve to say he can run Southern Rail when the Surbiton Crescent fiasco he is funding is causing such mayhem
@ChristineElmer @kevinjdavis @RBKingston What we need to know now is Who is to BLAME? Who on the council is going down for this fiasco?
@DannyPuffett @RBKingston @ContactKingston @kevinjdavis Totally agree. But this arrogant, useless/evil (take your pick) council won't listen
Surbiton Crescent fiasco presents reputational dilemma to @TfL as they are funding @RBKingston incompetence. It damages everyone it touches.
@rcfoster Generous London taxes pay for this Surbiton Crescent "car v cycle" war via @TfL £32.7m grant! All London shd revolt! @RBKingston</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
Think this is right. Local parties now presumably wary of candidates who might not be prepared to stick around. https://t.co/nMBjc1yWwY
@BBCJLandale Stick it in the Gallery. (Or the V&amp;A?)
@perkinscomment @chiggi Or maybe the new Arnold Bennett that is @sathnam? https://t.co/Niw5c8qfXe
RT @steverichards14: T Hunt's resignation-highlights Labour's fragility but also some dissenters' lack of appetite for the long haul, a dif…
@rafaelbehr @Samfr To hold Copeland isn't JC going to have have another of his reassessments of a core belief, this time on nuclear?
@NickCohen4 @Kevin_Maguire I only deploy the invective when I'm bigger than my interlocutor. Which is never.
@AdamBehrLive Yes indeed: "People of Stoke! Comrades! I have nothing to offer but my sword of genius..."
@Kevin_Maguire I know he was once DPM and all that but couldn't he have either called you "Mr Maguire" or perhaps just "Kevin"?
@thom_brooks Haha it was too early and I typed too fast and got my Engels and Hegel in a twist. Nasty. Bad dialectic.
@MarinaHyde @MichaelPDeacon I hope one person in the crowd that day mumbled "I'm not..."</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
Super Mario Run set to appear in App Store between 1800-1830 GMT , according to our sources, thanks @Tim
RT @NorthwichVicsFC: #Vics' supporters' &amp; @nvfcsa - Please read, and then share the attached letter. The Club need your help. Thankyou. 💚 @…
@Tim on Apple's revolutionary new device - no battery required, made of paper $aapl https://t.co/7sY2sAWWvw
Apple's latest product is a $300 book! $aapl https://t.co/nyOKQJdvWF
My dad, interviewed by The Guardian, the day before he died last month @NorthwichVicsFC https://t.co/yqRaXGGe1x
@FT US election coverage free to read from now https://t.co/phlyxobmjm
RT @VicsNews: WOW what a turn-out &amp; lovely service for DEREK today - i know you were looking down proud 😇#YouCantBeReplaced 💚🙌 #VicsLegend…
RT @simmo_on_sport: 💬 "If ever there was a one-club man it was Derek."

Tributes for @NorthwichVicsFC chairman have been warm.

📰 Words: ht…
RT @NorthwichNews: Northwich Victoria chairman dies age 89: Derek Nuttall had supported the club since he was a schoolboy https://t.co/k69e…
On behalf of my mum and the family, I'd like to thank everyone for their kind words and condolences for my dad toda… https://t.co/b0fVSateOp</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
Did you miss the FT's Business Book Challenge podcast series? Catch up on all 7 episodes here:… https://t.co/NeRsqOmLLY
How ‘death by overwork’ in Japan is exposing dangers of overtime culture: https://t.co/ENJGhTbOfg https://t.co/DSMXSVkjyU
Can male #MBA students put an end to sexism at work? Join the debate with our readers: https://t.co/zQEBVEMWkm https://t.co/Es4WShpYKD
Both men and women struggled at the top in the 1970s, says one FT reader. Share your experience of the workplace:… https://t.co/2R8fust2gy
How ‘death by overwork’ in Japan is exposing dangers of overtime culture: https://t.co/Jj7AkzkHlB https://t.co/IbwA7ANcq4
How Generator's "upscale" hostels are luring young business travellers away from hotels: https://t.co/KIvZSR51RD https://t.co/gN0LprUewC
Thinking of selling your home? Cheaper online portals are starting to gain ground from traditional estate agents:… https://t.co/sD6iwVw59p
How to write a business book and be a published author: https://t.co/X29bSJsS6C #businessbooks #management https://t.co/p5R4ITBFy4
How are MBAs putting an end to sexism at work? Readers have made some interesting comments. Join the debate:… https://t.co/AzrIsnIjWl
How getting an apology right can make you look good: https://t.co/tulLX5KyRL https://t.co/4IoIjV2V4D</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
RT @MITSloan: MIT Sloan Prof. Katherine Kellogg has been honored as Committed to Caring, going above and beyond for grad students. https://…
RT @deaneckles: Embarrassment of riches in models of diffusion (Granovetter vs. Bikhchandani, Hirshleifer &amp; Welch) by @duncanjwatts https:/…
RT @deaneckles: Nice examples of inferring causal relationship from observational data going wrong https://t.co/jlcyktHpOG from @ronnyk ht…
Parents--learn what your kids are doing instead of studying. Perfect review of LinkedIn--"ugh" by @thatswattsup https://t.co/39JVW3LIdk
RT @adchamberlain: Does more money make you happier at work? Terrific new academic paper using @Glassdoor data. https://t.co/e69Mfg7QI6 htt…
RT @dafrankel: A Half-Dozen Ways to Look at the Unit Economics of a Business https://t.co/TGQjnYAd85 via @wordpressdotcom
@Apple top-down approach works best if key decisions (e.g., design) can be concentrated at top &amp; genius at top.  https://t.co/B8AyZg7i4e
Congrats Nonny on winning Knight Innovation Award! @ImmersiveJourno pioneered #VR in journalism. Well done.… https://t.co/VLVBfBJahF
@johnvanreenen awarded OBE in New Years' Honors. Pioneered rigorous measurement of impact of management practices.  https://t.co/5zrGoviYUi
RT @OhGodItsAlexis: Hey @harvardlampoon pretty good book! i particularly like page 246, best page by far (that's mine. My piece is on that…</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFollowing>
Fiat under fire, how to lose $1bn, China rules the waves https://t.co/swJHSQNEB3
Indonesia eases ban on mineral exports https://t.co/Z5VzOmpFEz
Tillerson’s attack on China adds to the tension https://t.co/qdV138GVGi
Obama takes parting shot at China with WTO case https://t.co/rHtUcsomUH
How China rules the waves https://t.co/Xi9GCsT3js
Business should assume a hard Brexit https://t.co/b0dVLdm0VB
Free Lunch:  How storytelling can affect economics https://t.co/507egKOJZh
Offshore renminbi in multi-month show of strength https://t.co/EwPIIklnc9
AI arms race risks spiralling out of control, report warns https://t.co/CdhtMAWpu2
China tourist boom in S Korea belies defence spat https://t.co/PT6Wjz3A5L</tweetsFollowing>
    <tweetsFriends>
You know when you see a Tweet that's just, brilliant? Here are the Tweets we wish we wrote: https://t.co/gUVpZ481Co https://t.co/KW1EKaJ1WS
What should you post on Instagram? https://t.co/xsJMXQ15B8 6 types of content that work https://t.co/V7eSs9pS1E
Make the most of GIFs in your social media strategy: https://t.co/46PhWT7ceE The ultimate GIF guide https://t.co/VhJ9ALTURd
Want to increase your Twitter engagement? Here's a 5-day plan: https://t.co/qHRJQBgiCj https://t.co/F2HG95Bv25
Strapped for time and ideas? There’s no need to panic: https://t.co/b5HdOiElMd 10 content ideas that work https://t.co/beLO4XEGFw
How to launch and grow your YouTube channel subscribers and views in 14 days: https://t.co/rPkPB7icXN https://t.co/nYO3BJHyv4
Have you been neglecting your LinkedIn profile? https://t.co/AgCRG2fOY6 5 easy ways to refresh your LinkedIn https://t.co/x0ZkINbDKU
Before you hit send on that social media post, ask yourself these 5 questions: https://t.co/abVNSF3WDR https://t.co/ZgoKKlpbRu
@GroundsYVR We really did! The whole office got a chance to enjoy them 👍
@evernote It's always a pleasure to spend the #HootChat hour discussing ideas with you!</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
.@DameStephanie_: Blazing a trail for women in tech https://t.co/e1RtNzIp9f
Business Book Challenge – a masterclass https://t.co/AJeiIByG9z
The Life of a Song: Stairway to Heaven https://t.co/d9XIoheXH2
Leaders under pressure: Denis Kozlowski 4/4 https://t.co/oly2gKMYfT
Leaders under pressure: Marcela Sapone https://t.co/B7CYFhT4gs
‘Pig-killing day’ by David Szalay https://t.co/MOBIm0pyiU
Leaders under pressure: Stephen Hester 2/4 https://t.co/HNYySHahWl
Leaders under pressure: Pascal Soriot 1/4 https://t.co/HKKlyWI7Px
2016 politics review https://t.co/ZbrVlDSGEq</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
Did you miss the FT's Business Book Challenge podcast series? Catch up on all 7 episodes here:… https://t.co/NeRsqOmLLY
How ‘death by overwork’ in Japan is exposing dangers of overtime culture: https://t.co/ENJGhTbOfg https://t.co/DSMXSVkjyU
Can male #MBA students put an end to sexism at work? Join the debate with our readers: https://t.co/zQEBVEMWkm https://t.co/Es4WShpYKD
Both men and women struggled at the top in the 1970s, says one FT reader. Share your experience of the workplace:… https://t.co/2R8fust2gy
How ‘death by overwork’ in Japan is exposing dangers of overtime culture: https://t.co/Jj7AkzkHlB https://t.co/IbwA7ANcq4
How Generator's "upscale" hostels are luring young business travellers away from hotels: https://t.co/KIvZSR51RD https://t.co/gN0LprUewC
Thinking of selling your home? Cheaper online portals are starting to gain ground from traditional estate agents:… https://t.co/sD6iwVw59p
How to write a business book and be a published author: https://t.co/X29bSJsS6C #businessbooks #management https://t.co/p5R4ITBFy4
How are MBAs putting an end to sexism at work? Readers have made some interesting comments. Join the debate:… https://t.co/AzrIsnIjWl
How getting an apology right can make you look good: https://t.co/tulLX5KyRL https://t.co/4IoIjV2V4D</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
Fiat under fire, how to lose $1bn, China rules the waves https://t.co/swJHSQNEB3
Indonesia eases ban on mineral exports https://t.co/Z5VzOmpFEz
Tillerson’s attack on China adds to the tension https://t.co/qdV138GVGi
Obama takes parting shot at China with WTO case https://t.co/rHtUcsomUH
How China rules the waves https://t.co/Xi9GCsT3js
Business should assume a hard Brexit https://t.co/b0dVLdm0VB
Free Lunch:  How storytelling can affect economics https://t.co/507egKOJZh
Offshore renminbi in multi-month show of strength https://t.co/EwPIIklnc9
AI arms race risks spiralling out of control, report warns https://t.co/CdhtMAWpu2
China tourist boom in S Korea belies defence spat https://t.co/PT6Wjz3A5L</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
Six financial personalities — which one are you? https://t.co/CiSGikrfEI
FT Money Show: What financial personality type are you? https://t.co/qPhXyPE8c2
Pensions first as scheme saved from lifeboat fund https://t.co/BkrWXuhqjr
RT @ClaerB: Conspiracy theory - is the horrible taste of HMRC's envelope gum a nudge to get us to pay #TaxReturns online? https://t.co/g8un…
Find the cheapest high street cup of coffee https://t.co/oCVVBsjeIJ
Your questions: Should I pay inheritance tax in the UK or Ireland? https://t.co/AGxbQo9EEk
Trump will struggle, but global stocks will boom — Ken Fisher https://t.co/PiTF9lpnhD https://t.co/tQpZx4Xbop
Time to find a car boot sale near you: how to profit from de-cluttering https://t.co/aMqzpVAch2
Trump will struggle — but global stocks will boom https://t.co/DA9cGhJN1M
UK investors thirsty for BrewDog https://t.co/SHWZALnC1M</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
RT @BraddJaffy: Here's the exchange where CNN's Jim @Acosta tries to ask Trump a question and the President-elect refuses https://t.co/Llwm…
RT @SebastianEPayne: Discussing #PMQs shortly on the @ft's Facebook page with @henrymance live from Westminster. Watch here https://t.co/Iu…
We're live with our Lex team - ask them your questions about the year's big business stories and 2017 predictions https://t.co/wv9m3dwRxQ
Inside Brexit: How Britain lost Europe. Political editor @GeorgeWParker finds the real story of the EU vote. Full:… https://t.co/Lg8D49T0oz
RT @FTMag: Life as an @MSF doctor in crisis zones: ‘You treat the victim but you also treat the killer.’ https://t.co/5Z1Gyq47UG https://t.…
We went stargazing with @neiltyson. See what we learnt in the full @FT video here: https://t.co/km8LkuJan8 https://t.co/c0CjmsLZfV
RT @ftvideo: Was Brexit inevitable? Ask our political and Brexit editors in a live discussion now: https://t.co/wv9m3dwRxQ
Was Brexit inevitable? Ask our political and Brexit editors in a live discussion now: https://t.co/wv9m3dwRxQ
Haiti's expecting mothers and their babies face terrible odds. @FT's @jude_webber on @MSF's efforts to better them https://t.co/xxo15F2MA8
Immersive narratives and emotion in digital storytelling at the News Impact Summit today in Amsterdam #NISAMS</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
Tillerson’s attack on China adds to the tension https://t.co/v1RHrhTnku
Investment in green energy falls 18% https://t.co/XOLp9NarzF
Obama takes parting shot at China with WTO case https://t.co/qfBS56B7VA
Bricks-and-mortar shops enjoy renaissance in China https://t.co/mAGOSwL4jV
How China rules the waves https://t.co/nLXF7HNrOc
Tillerson sets stage for clash over South China Sea https://t.co/C54O8rAGG0
China groups insured against blocked foreign deals https://t.co/HASxlwGM9O
China tourist boom in S Korea belies defence spat https://t.co/XKAlNZ0Ndj
Shanghai Tower: how China’s tallest skyscraper was built https://t.co/g4cplRUV1C
Chinese FDI into EU dwarfs flow in other direction https://t.co/i4mETDA4Eb</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
RT @fastFT: Labour MP Tristram Hunt quits triggering by-election https://t.co/1hEkbOIJzy
Where does a 747 pilot go when he has time to himself? https://t.co/wBdZSkUWsu https://t.co/qR1q1Wo0YP
'Cuddle up to the Kremlin and do not be surprised when you are burnt.' https://t.co/H4cPNEh5kR https://t.co/hjVpBdNg27
A darling of the nascent drone industry has collapsed after collecting $34m in pre-orders https://t.co/4L5wTJsMgs
Something has gone unexpectedly right on London's high street. https://t.co/IJEUfgRdIj
FT View: Donald Trump’s abject failure on conflicts of interest https://t.co/oiDxY2LArh https://t.co/6hVpc1VlJ2
RT @michaellachlan: Global oil flow trackers set to keep Opec honest https://t.co/2E9kT9IPxy via @FT
The so-called wet-foot, dry-foot policy has long angered the Cuban government. https://t.co/obXQ9uOyCt
This is good news for Angela Merkel's re-election hopes https://t.co/7WpDYam9fb
Scientists have figured out how to use lasers to instantly turn mild-mannered mice into ferocious predators… https://t.co/cnbAuXdwlx</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
The Winklevoss twins - remember them? Now, after Facebook, is Bitcoin is the future? FREE TO READ - https://t.co/pCNlYUiZ40 … @ftmoney
Ever wondered what presidents of The Oxford Union do next? Politics, surely - or business? https://t.co/f7BR8GRYYL @miss_marriage @ftmoney
Melissa Berman of Rockefeller Philanthropy Advisors - changing the way donors think https://t.co/lXMi3z3et2 @sarahgor @ftmoney @ft
2 out of every 5 retired footballers go bankrupt. Ouch. But now theyre becoming moguls off the pitch - https://t.co/koobPjmuoF @ft
@ftmoney
How do you create a child genius? Psychologist and author Oliver James (of Affluenza fame) has a plan: https://t.co/GFIK8rbLzC @ftmoney @FT
SocGen moves to combine its two private banking divisions. Arise Kleinwort Hambros @ftmoney
Close Brothers reports increase in loan book: https://t.co/ukjW0bZo6q … @ftmoney
Fabulous report on maternal and child health from @FT today - https://t.co/CQnJPOmCFM … @crabtreemi @ftreports @ftbirth
Handbags at dawn: they might actually be worth a fortune - https://t.co/KA3JorZ4S7 @ftmoney
Hoorah! @ft_wealth magazine out today with the @FT. Fantastic cover story by @stephenfoley on how scions of the wealthy are making an impact</tweetsFriends>
    <tweetsFriends>
Can male #MBA students put an end to sexism at work? Join the debate: https://t.co/8IZQXGn2Nr https://t.co/AF0VDD6rea
A review of the $10,000 nano-MBA programme run by Stanford Graduate School of Business: https://t.co/8qpvrxMHDw https://t.co/MvHnKVl3hm
Is your business in need of therapy? https://t.co/FyZWrdeyqr https://t.co/F2HmDvut1G
Both men and women struggle at the top, argues one reader in a debate on the need for #MBA 'manbassadors' - join in… https://t.co/ql2SVo21Ll
Can a male-led group at London Business School @LBS change sexist attitudes in the workplace? Join the debate:… https://t.co/JSWLWmrJWe
Should you study for an #MBA? Would-be students now question its value. Join the debate: https://t.co/QNKLFeRkWD https://t.co/UbLLtNi1W2
Male MBA students and sexist managers https://t.co/iqCsCIfGgC
Review – Stanford’s Ignite course for start-ups https://t.co/GHr7AyYclE
Said Business School acts to head off Brexit risk https://t.co/cH3xBbZ1qx
The best thing I read all year — 2016 https://t.co/nqPVdlwWeV</tweetsFriends>
</user>
